http://www.louthplaygoers.co.uk/codes-and-policies

Virtual Christmas Fair/
Lockdown/Lockdown LibraryLockdown CreationsMurder Mystery Trail
What's On/
About Us/About UsCOVID-19 InformationAccessibilityCodes and PoliciesArts AwardReservations & Refund PolicyReviews
Virtual Christmas Fair/
Lockdown/Lockdown LibraryLockdown CreationsMurder Mystery Trail
What's On/
About Us/About UsCOVID-19 InformationAccessibilityCodes and PoliciesArts AwardReservations & Refund PolicyReviews
Youth Theatre/Riverhead Youth TheatreRiverhead Producers
Riverhead Gallery/
Contact / Find Us/
PoliciesIt is the aim of Louth Playgoers Society Ltd to create a supportive and respectful environment where people are able to access our services, building and staff teams to further their understanding and enjoyment of theatre, the arts and the creative process.On this page you will find supporting documents from our codes and policies.The files are in PDF format. Code of ConductEquality and DiversityWhistleblowing PolicyGrievance PolicySafeguarding PolicySocial Media PolicyComplaints PolicyData Management PolicyDisciplinary PolicyHarassment PolicyHealth & Safety PolicyLone Working PolicyHow we use your personal informationJump straight to:Privacy noticeCookie policy Privacy noticeLouth Playgoers Society Ltd. Respects Your Privacy Louth Playgoers Society Ltd is a registered charity no. 1078605. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will only use your personal information in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant legislation.Our Privacy Policy is set out below: please read it with care as it describes how we will process your data and that of your children.Data Security and StorageWe collect and store personal and non-personal data that you may volunteer as part of booking tickets, making a purchase, becoming a Member or via donation forms, e-news sign-ups, visitor surveys or in connection with a specific project or event.Personal information we collect may include: Your full name and title and date of birthPostal address, email address and phone numberIP (internet protocol) addressTicket purchase historyYour contact and communication preferences – the information you have opted to receive from The Riverhead Theatre about our programmes and how you want to receive thisNon-personal information we collect includes: IP addresses (the location of the computer on the internet); web pages accessed; and files downloaded. This helps us to determine how many people use our website, how regularly they visit, and how popular our webpages are. This information does not tell us anything about who you are or where you live, but it does help us monitor and improve our service.We store personal data under strict safekeeping and confidentiality measures on secure servers operated by Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. and stored securely by Seat Advisor, our ticketing, marketing and fundraising systems provider. Seat Advisor is a cloud-based solution and are PCI Level 1 compliant which is the most stringent level of certification available in the payments industry. Only authorised Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. staff who need to process your data will have access to it.By disclosing your personal information to us via Louth Playgoers Society Ltd, by phone, website, email or in writing, you are giving us your consent to collect, store and process your personal information in the manner described in this Notice. The information we hold will be accurate and up-to-date within our knowledge.While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur when it is under our control, we use our best efforts to try to prevent this. Unfortunately, the transmission of data across the internet is not completely secure and while we do our best to try to protect the security of your information we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur while data is being transferred.If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Notice or your information, please email: admin@louthplaygoers.co.uk or write to Data Protection, The Riverhead Theatre, Victoria Road, Louth LN11 0BX.We will use the information you provide to:Process sales transactions, donations or other payments and verify financial transactionsFulfil your requests – such as applications for membership, donations, competition entries, participation in campaigns and provision of informationHandle and deliver orders and communicate with you about themProvide a personalised service to you when you visit our website. This could include customising the content and/or layout of our pages for individual usersRecord any contact we have with youPrevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf in relation to prevention and detectionCarry out research on the demographics, interests and behaviour of our users and supporters to help Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. gain a better understanding of them and to enable us to improve our service. This research is usually carried out internally by our employees unless we notify you otherwise and have your prior consent.Communicate with our customers and supportersSharing informationTo undertake our business activities we sometimes have to share your information with third parties such as our database and IT providers and our mailing house, which handles our direct postal communications with you. We only choose partners we trust and will only pass personal data to them if they have signed a contract that requires them to:abide by the requirements of the Data Protection Acttreat your information as carefully as we wouldonly use the information for the purposes it was supplied (and not for their own purposes or the purposes of any other organisation)allow us to carry out checks to ensure they are doing all these things.Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. is part of a Lincolnshire (LOV) National Portfolio Organisation (NPO) and as such receives public funding from Arts Council England. We are therefore required to collaborate with and share personal customer data with other NPOs. This information is only used by publicly-funded arts organisations in England to better understand their audiences and improve their cultural offer. Children and Vulnerable AdultsWe are committed to safeguarding children, young people and vulnerable adults and do all we can to ensure that all who work at Louth Playgoers Society Ltd., including volunteers, whether on stage or joining a Youth Group, are safe and inspired by their experience. An important part of doing this is to protect their privacy.The Theatre does have an obligation for all young people taking part in productions to share information with Children in Entertainment and Employment (CEE) at Lincolnshire County Council as part of the Performance Licence Application process. However, these details will not be stored by us electronically AFTER the show. This information will be deleted as paper copies are kept for 6 months and then destroyed. In the instance where a concern is raised around safeguarding, records will be retained under safeguarding measures and Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. will still be compliant with the law. For example where a volunteer has received a warning about behaviour or asked to leave the society over concerns around safeguarding the company will still retain information and data for safeguarding purposes. If you are aged 18 or under, please obtain your parent / guardian’s permission every time before you provide any personal information; we will always require their signature on any documentation when you sign up to a Louth Playgoers Society Ltd. project or are contracted to perform with us. We will always require the carer’s signature on similar documentation relating to vulnerable adults.ContinuationThe permissions above relate to optional communications from Louth Playgoers Society Ltd.. We will continue to send you communications about transactions you make with us, for example when you purchase tickets or relating to active subscriptions you hold with us such as a membership. We will consider that your preferences last for five years unless you notify us otherwise. Cookie policyLouth Playgoers Society Ltd.Louth Playgoers Society Ltd is a registered charity no. 1078605. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will only use your personal information in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant legislation.About the cookies we useWe use cookies to help our site run effectively and provide the best experience for visitors. What are cookies?Cookies are small pieces of data that websites store on a device. Cookies can improve your and your visitors’ browsing experience because they help websites remember preferences and understand how people use different features.Functional and Required CookiesWe use some necessary cookies because they allow visitors to navigate and use key features on your site. These cookies vary depending on the features you use on our site. The cookies we may use are:
Cookie name
Duration
Purpose
Crumb
Session
Prevents cross-site request forgery (CSRF). CSRF is an attack vector that tricks a browser into taking unwanted action in an application when someone’s logged in.
RecentRedirect
30 minutes
Prevents redirect loops if a site has custom URL redirects.
Locked
Session
Prevents the password-protected screen from displaying if a visitor enters the correct site-wide password.
SiteUserInfo
3 years
Identifies a visitor who logs into a customer account
SiteUserSecureAuthToken
3 years
Authenticates a visitor who logs into a customer account
squarespace-popup-overlay
Persistent
Prevents the Promotional Pop-Up from displaying if a visitor dismisses it
squarespace-announcement-bar
Persistent
Prevents the Announcement Bar from displaying if a visitor dismisses it
Analytics and Performance CookiesWe use Analytics and Performance cookies to collect information about how visitors interact with our site. Storing these cookies allows us to analyse how visitors use our site in order to improve it and make it more effective.
Cookie name
Duration
Purpose
ss_cid
2 years
Identifies unique visitors and tracks a visitor’s sessions on a site
ss_cvr
2 years
Identifies unique visitors and tracks a visitor’s sessions on a site
ss_cvisit
30 minutes
Identifies unique visitors and tracks a visitor’s sessions on a site
ss_cvt
30 minutes
Identifies unique visitors and tracks a visitor’s sessions on a site
ss_cpvisit
2 years
Identifies unique visitors and tracks a visitor’s sessions on a site
ss_cookieAllowed
30 days
Remembers if a visitor agreed to placing Analytics cookies on their browser if a site is restricting the placement of cookies
Home/
Virtual Christmas Fair/
Lockdown/Lockdown LibraryLockdown CreationsMurder Mystery Trail
What's On/
About Us/About UsCOVID-19 InformationAccessibilityCodes and PoliciesArts AwardReservations & Refund PolicyReviews
Youth Theatre/Riverhead Youth TheatreRiverhead Producers
Riverhead Gallery/
Contact / Find Us/
Louth Riverhead Theatre
Louth Riverhead Theatre is owned and operated by Louth Playgoers Society Ltd.
My Basket
0 item(s)
|
Total:
The Box Office is open for advanced booking every Monday to Saturday from 10.00am – 1.00pm.
Order refreshments safely and securely from your own device.
Click here for the app.
Louth Riverhead Theatre is owned and operated by Louth Playgoers Society Ltd.Copyright Louth Playgoers Society. All images are Copyright.
